A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Council on Indians, 1988-2012
Library of Virginia
- Series II. Planning documents, 1988-2012., Extent: 13 cu. ft. (13 boxes).
  - Archaeological reviews, 1988-2012., 10 cu. ft. (10 boxes)
    - United States Army Corps of Engineers, 1998-2011.
      - Draft Report, Data Recovery Excavations at the Former American Viscose Plant (44RN348), City of Roanoke, Roanoke County, Virginia, 2007 November. (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Mitigation Bank Prospectus, Proposed Lone Oak Mitigation Bank, Albemarle County, Virginia, 2008 January. (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Draft Report, Archeological Deep Testing at the Blue Ridge Industrial Park and Bridge Street Areas, City of Roanoke, Roanoke County, Virginia, 2008 February. (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Final Report, Data Recovery Excavations at the Former American Viscose Plant (44RN348), City of Roanoke, Roanoke County, Virginia, 2007 November. (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Final Report, Archaeological Data Recovery Investigations: Maher Field Site (44RN221), Roanoke City Schools Maintenance and Operational Center Parking Lot, City of Roanoke, Roanoke County, Virginia, 2008 December. (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Final Report, Archeological Deep Testing at the Blue Ridge Industrial Park and Bridge Street Areas, City of Roanoke, Roanoke County, Virginia, 2009 March. (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Draft Report, Archeological Investigations at Late Woodland Site 44RN356, City of Roanoke, Roanoke County, Virginia, 2009 May. (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Final Report, Archeological Investigations at Late Woodland Site 44RN356, City of Roanoke, Roanoke County, Virginia, 2009 May. (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Archeological Investigations at the APCO Site (44RN219), City of Roanoke, Roanoke County, Virginia, 2009 July. (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Environmental Assessment, Recreation Trail Above Wasena Park, Roanoke River Flood Reduction Project Upper Basin, Roanoke, Virginia, 2009 December. (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Archeological Investigations at the APCO Site (44RN219), City of Roanoke, Roanoke County, Virginia, Final Report, 2010 January. (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - Phase II Archeological Evaluation of Site 44CF568, Defense Supply Center Richmond, Chesterfield County, Virginia, 2010 May. (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - Environmental Assessment, Shoreline Stabilization, John H. Kerr Reservoir, Boydton, Virginia, 2010 December. (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - Occoneechee State Park Marina Environmental Assessment, John H. Kerr Dam and Reservoir, 2011 February. (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - Integrated Cultural Resource Management Plan (2011-2016), Arlington National Cemetery, Arlington, Virginia, 2011 November. (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - United States Coast Guard, 2010.
      - Phase I Archaeological Survey of Waterline Service Upgrade Corridors for the United States Coast Guard Training Center, Yorktown, Virginia, 2010 September. (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - United States Customs and Border Protection, 2008.
      - Determination of No Historic Properties Affected under Section 106 of the National Historic Preservation Act for the Stafford Facility at Hartwood, Stafford and Fauquier Counties, Virginia, 2008 June. (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - United States Navy, 2004-2009.
      - Archaeological Evidence for Native Prestige Commodity Devaluation: An Example from the Chesapeake Associated with the Jamestown Colony, 2004 June. (Box 14, Folder 19)
      - Section 106 Consultation Environmental Impact Statement for OUtdoor Research, Development, Test and Evaluation Activities, Naval Surface Warfare Center, Dahlgren Site, NSF Dahlgren, Virginia, 2009 Jan. (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - U.S. Home, 2006.
      - Phase II Archaeological Testing of Site 44JC1146 and Additional Phase I Archaeological Survey of an Area of Potential Effect at the Boy Scout Tract, James City County, Virginia, 2006 March 21. (Box 14, Folder 21)
      - Phase I Archaeological Survey of Ten Areas of Potential Effect at the BSA Tract in James City County, Virginia, 2006 April 7. (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Virginia Air National Guard, 2009.
      - Environmental Assessment and Preliminary Section 106 Effects Assessment for Construction Program, State Military Reservation Camp Pendleton, City of Virginia Beach, Virginia, 2009 May. (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Virginia Department of Conservation and Recreation, 2004.
      - Draft Environmental Assessment, Construction of Visitor Facilities at Occoneechee State Park, Mecklenburg County, Virginia, 2004 August. (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Virginia Department of Military Affairs, 2005-2007.
      - Final Environmental Assessment, Future Mission Requirements 2005, Virginia Army National Guard, Maneuver Training Center, Fort Pickett, Blackstone, Virginia, 2005 July. (Box 14, Folder 25)
      - Integrated Cultural Resources Management Plan for the Facilities of the Virginia Army National Guard, 2007-2011, 2007 January. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Department of Transportation, 1991-2010.
      - Phase III Archaeological Investigations of the "522 Bridge Site" (44WR329), Warren County, Virginia, 1991 May. (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Archaeological Site Evaluations at Sites 44R451 and 44RB462, Route 130, Near the Town of Glasgow, Rockbridge County, Virginia, 2001 May. (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Archaeological Data Recovery at the Brook Run Jasper Quarry (Site 44CU122) Associated with the Proposed Route 3 Improvements, Culpeper County, Virginia, 2004 February. (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Additional Archaeological Evaluation of Site 44WR329, Proposed Route 340 Bridge Replacement Project, Warren County, Virginia: An Addendum to Phase III Archaeological Investigations of the "522 Bridge Site" (44WR329), Warren County, Virginia, 2004 February. (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Stratified Archaic and Woodland Occupations in the James River Piedmont: Archaeological Data Recovery at Site 44PO81, Associated with the Route 288 Project, Powhatan County, Virginia, 2004 May 19. (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Archaeological Survey, Proposed Relocation of Kings Highway Bridge, Route 125, Suffolk Virginia, 2004 October. (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Archaeological Survey and Evaluation of Mount Airy Site (44RD3), Route 624 (Newland Road), Richmond County, Virginia,. (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Terrestrial and Submerged Cultural Resources Archaeological Survey, Judith Stewart Dresser Memorial Bridge Replacement (Route 5) and Archaeological Evaluation of Site 44JC1123, Charles City and James City Counties, Virginia, 2005 May. (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - ARchaeological Evaluation of Sites 44PW1226 and 44PW1227 Improvements to U.S. Route 1 (Jefferson Davis Highway), Prince William County, Virginia, 2005 August. (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Data Recovery at Sites 44SN243 and 44SN245, Southampton County, Virginia, 2005 September. (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Cultural Resource Survey of Route 30 (Kings Dominion Boulevard/Dawn Boulevard) State Fair Project, Caroline and Hanover Counties, Virginia, 2005 December. (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Archaeological Survey of the Proposed Route 205 Project, Westmoreland County, Virginia, 2008 February. (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - Archaeological Evaluation and Archaeological Data Recovery Excavations at Site 44CE0010, Caroline County, Virginia, 2008 February. (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - Archaeological Data Recovery Excavations at the Locher Site (44RB0451) and Echols Farm Site (44RB0462) Alternative 3A Route 130, Rockbridge County, Virginia, 2008 April. (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - An Archaeological Evaluation of Site 44WM0304, Proposed Route 205 Project, Westmoreland County, Virginia, 2008 May 9. (Box 15, Folder 16)
      - Phase II Archaeological Evaluation of Site 44ST0971 for the Proposed I-95 PPTA HOT Lanes Project, Stafford County, Virginia, 2009 February. (Box 15, Folder 17)
      - Archaeological Survey and Evaluation of a Civil War Campsite (44ST1048), I-95 PPTA HOT Lanes, Stafford County, Virginia, 2009 March. (Box 15, Folder 18)
      - Management Summary for the Phase I Architectural Survey for the I-95 HOT Lanes (South), Stafford and Spotsylvania Counties and the City of Fredericksburg, Virginia, 2009 March 30. (Box 15, Folder 19)
      - Archaeological Evaluation of Sites 44ST0309, 44ST0311, 44ST0960, 44ST0962, and 44ST0963 in Association with the Proposed I-95 HOT Lanes Project, Stafford County, Virginia, 2009 May 8. (Box 15, Folder 20)
      - Cultural Resource Survey and Archaeological Evaluations of Four Sites in Association with Proposed Replacement of the Route 340/522 Bridge Over the South Fork of the Shenandoah River, 2009 June. (Box 15, Folder 21)
      - Cultural Resource Survey and Archaeological Evaluation of Site 44GS0012 in Association with Proposed Replacement of the Route 61 Bridge over the New River, Giles County, Virginia, 2009 August. (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Archaeological Survey and Evaluation of Site 44WR0224 in Association with Proposed Replacement of the Route 340/522 Bridge over the South Fork of the Shenandoah River, Warren County, Virginia, 2009 November. (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Archaeological Survey of Proposed Bridge Replacement over Battle Run on Richmond Road, Rappahannock County, Virginia, 2010 June. (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Archaeological Survey of Proposed Bridge Replacement over Herring Creek on West River Road, King William County, Virginia, 2010 September. (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Phase II Cultural Resources Evaluation of Site 44KW0296, Bridge Replacement over Herring Creek, King William County, Virginia, 2010 November. (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - White Oak Land Company, 2008.
      - Phase I Cultural Resource Survey of the 20-acre White Oak Mitigation Bank, Buckingham County, Virginia, 2008 June 9. (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Phase I Cultural Recognition Survey of the 20-acre White Oak Mitigation Bank, Buckingham County, Virginia, 2008 June 15. (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Williamsburg Environmental Group, 2003-2011.
      - Phase I Archaeological Survey of Approximately 170 Acres at the Proposed Marine Container Terminal Facility, City of Portsmouth, Virginia, 2003 December. (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Phase II Evaluation of Sites 44PM12 and 44PM13 at the APM Terminals, City of Portsmouth, Virginia, 2004 February. (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Draft Treatment Plan, Archaeological Data Recovery at Sites 44PM12 and 44PM13, APM Terminals, City of Portsmouth, Virginia, 2004 May 18. (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Final Treatment Plan, Archaeological Data Recovery at Sites 44PM12 and 44PM13, APM Terminals, City of Portsmouth, Virginia, 2004 June 24. (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Interim Report, Archaeological Data Recovery at Site 44PM13A, APM Terminals, City of Portsmouth, Virginia, 2004 September. (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - Phase III Archaeological Data Recovery at Sites 44PM0012 and 44PM0013, APM Terminals, City of Portsmouth, Virginia, Volume I: Technical Report, 2006 April. (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - Phase III Archaeological Data Recovery at Sites 44PM0012 and 44PM0013, APM Terminals, City of Portsmouth, Virginia, Volume I: Technical Report, 2006 April. (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - Phase I Cultural Resource Survey, John Rolfe Parkway, Henrico County, Virginia Addendum: Supplemental Phase I Cultural Resources Survey for the Current Proposed Alignment for the John Rolfe Parkway, 2006 November. (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - Phase I Archaeological Survey of Twelve Army Corps of Engineers Designated Areas of Potential Effect Located Within the Proposed Ridings Subdivision, Henrico County, Virginia, 2007 February. (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - Phase IA Cultural Resources Assessment and Proposed Research Design for the Proposed Mitigation Banks on the Pamunkey River in New Kent County, Virginia, 2007 June. (Box 16, Folder 17)
      - Draft Phase I Archaeological Survey of Approximately 121 Acres Within the Proposed Pamunkey Farms Mitigation Bank in New Kent County, Virginia, 2007 September. (Box 16, Folder 18)
      - Revised Draft Phase I Archaeological Survey of Approximately 121 Acres Within the Proposed Pamunkey Farms Mitigation Bank in New Kent County, Virginia, 2008 March. (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - Final Phase I Archaeological Survey of Approximately 121 Acres Within the Proposed Pamunkey Farms Mitigation Bank in New Kent County, Virginia, 2008 April. (Box 16, Folder 20)
      - Phase I Cultural Resources Survey of Permit Areas Within the Bottoms Bride Tract, New Kent County, Virginia, 2008 August. (Box 16, Folder 21)
      - Environmental Assessment, The Cove Project at J.H. Kerr Reservoir, Town of Clarksville, Virginia, 2010 August. (Box 16, Folder 22)
      - Phase IA Cultural Resources Assessment of Approximately 420 Acres for the Proposed Reedy Creek Farm Mitigation Bank, Dinwiddie County, Virginia, 2011 September. (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Subject files, 1997-2012., 3 cu. ft. (3 boxes)
    Subject files, 1997-2012, typically involving consultations with federal agencies, state agencies, and private companies through Section 106 of the National Historic Preservation Act that were submitted to the Virginia Council on Indians for their comment. Includes correspondence, memoranda of understanding, programmatic agreements, and other related material.
    - King William Reservoir Mitigation Bank Proposals, 2007. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Bowen-Frazier Mitigation Bank, 2011. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - National Park Service First Century Project, 2004-2005. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Historic Jamestowne Visitors Center, 2005. (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - White Marsh/Grandview, 2007. (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Greensville County, 2012. (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - John H. Kerr Reservoir, 2006-2008. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Middle Peninsula Conservation Easement, 2010. (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - ASC Mitigation Bank, 2009. (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - AAA Environmental Bank, 2009. (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Blue Ridge Airport, 2009. (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Department of Transportation Agreement, 2009. (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Cobbs Creek, 2011. (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - National Resources Conservation Service: Pohick Dam, 2007. (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Bottoms Bridge Complex, 2008. (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Bottoms Bridge Hotel, 2008. (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Powhatan State Park Addition, 2010. (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Culpeper Regional Airport, 2008-2009. (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority, Washington County, 2009. (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Tazewell Bluestone Project, 2008-2009. (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Pamunkey Farms Wetlands Mitigation Bank, 2007. (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Brunswick County Mitigation Bank, 2010. (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - James River Mitigation Bank, 2009. (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Scandia Mitigation Bank, 2009. (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Fort Story Project, 2006-2007. (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Fort Story, 2006. (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Chippokes State Park, 2008. (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Washington-Rochambeau Revolutionary Route, 2005. (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Barrett's Ferry Bridge, 2005. (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Cumberland Dams, 2010. (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Plum Tree Island, 2005-2006. (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Broad Street Bus Rapid Transit Project, 2010. (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Dominion: North Anna Power Plant, 2011. (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Chesterfield Power Station, 2010. (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - South Boston Energy, 2010. (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Wythe County Progress Park, 2011. (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Lyndham Hill, 2012. (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Froehling and Robertson, 2008-2011. (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - ATC Associates, 2010-2011. (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Advantage Environmental Consultants, 2009-2011. (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Battersea, 2011. (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Hull Springs Farm Mitigation Bank, undated. (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Periwinkle Branch, 2009. (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Mt. Stirling-Bailey Mitigation Bank, 2008. (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Washington County Service Authority, 2009. (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Norfolk Naval Shipyard Portsmouth, 2009. (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Virginia Railway Express, 2010. (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Southeast High Speed Rail, 2010. (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Middle Peninsula Park, 2009-2010. (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Hillpoint, 2011. (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Hillpoint Estates, 2010-2011. (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - Belle Isle Shoreline Restoration, 2011. (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Patriot Pipeline, 2004. (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - Hardy Transmission Project, 2004-2008. (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - Columbia Gas Transmission Gala Site, 2001-2008. (Box 17, Folder 55)
    - Federal Energy Regulatory Commission Gas Projects, 2004-2005. (Box 17, Folder 56)
    - Mid-Atlantic Connector, 2010. (Box 17, Folder 57)
    - Army Corps of Engineers, Norfolk District, 2004-2005. (Box 17, Folder 58)
    - City of Lynchburg, 2006. (Box 17, Folder 59)
    - Rails for Trails, 2004. (Box 17, Folder 60)
    - Richmond Housing and Urban Development, 2004-2005. (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - Roanoke Flood Wall, 2003-2005. (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - Roanoke Flood Wall, 2008. (Box 17, Folder 63)
    - Chisel Run, 2004. (Box 17, Folder 64)
    - Kiskiack, 2003-2004. (Box 17, Folder 65)
    - Occoneechee State Park Campbell Camp, 2007. (Box 17, Folder 66)
    - Occoneechee State Park, undated. (Box 17, Folder 67)
    - Patriots Landing, 2005. (Box 17, Folder 68)
    - Dulles Airport, 2005. (Box 17, Folder 69)
    - Kings Highway Project, 2004-2007. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Army Corps of Engineers: Nottoway River Concord School, 2004. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - William and Mary, 2004. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Department of Transportation: Nottoway River Site, 2003. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Potomac Creek, 2003. (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - United States Fish and Wildlife Service, 2005. (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Exmore-Nassawaddox, 2005. (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Portsmouth Terminals, 2003-2006. (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Portsmouth Terminals, 2004. (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Route 1 Corridor Improvements, 2006. (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Cane Creek, 2006. (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Deshazo Site, 1997. (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Bridge Renaming Idea, 2005. (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Natural Resources Partnership, 2005. (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Caroline County Query, 2008. (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Camp Peary, 2008. (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Camp Peary, 2009. (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Hampton Roads Sanitation District, 2008-2009. (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Fort Belvoir Base Realignment and Closure Commission, 2003-2011. (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - North Anna Power Station, 2008. (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, 2007. (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Hercules Site, 2004-2007. (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Giles County Route 61 Replacement Bridge, 2009. (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - John Rolfe Parkway, 2007. (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - John Rolfe Parkway, 2006. (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Route 130 over the Maury River, 2005-2006. (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Maury River Bridge, 2005. (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Eastern Market Expansion Project, 2006. (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Route 3 Widening, 2011. (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Virginia Department of Transportation: Route 30, 2005-2006. (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Route 340 Bridge, 2004-2011. (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Peleg's Point, 2004-2007. (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Lyndham Hill, 2012. (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Ragged Mountain Reservoir, 2007. (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Route 205 in Westmoreland County, 2008-2010. (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Route 205 Bridge, 2010. (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - New River Gorge, 2006. (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - City Point, 2004-2005. (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - City Point, 2006. (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Fort Monroe Interpretive Master Plan, 2009-2010. (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Prince William Forest Park, 2011. (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Fort Pickett, 2005. (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - United States Department of Agriculture, 2005. (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Privitized Military Housing, 2005. (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Federal Emergency Management Agency, 2003-2009. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Fort Pickett, 2009. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Langley Air Force Base, 2006. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Warrenton Training Center, 2012. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Naval Surface Warfare Center Dahlgren Division, undated. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Fort Pickett, 2009-2011. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Fort Eustis, 2003-2004. (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Fort Lee, 2004-2012. (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Fort Lee Base Realignment and Closure Commission, 2010. (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Farrar Island, 2011. (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Fort A.P. Hill Base Realignment and Closure Commission, 2007-2010. (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Fort A.P. Hill Mitigation Programmatic Agreement, 2007-2010. (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Fort Belvoir, 2012. (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Fort Monroe, 2004-2008. (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Fort Monroe Flood Control, 2005-2008. (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Harry W. Nice Bridge, 2010-2011. (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - George W. Nice Bridge, Highway 301, 2007-2010. (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Defense Supply Center Richmond, 2010. (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Defense Supply Center Richmond, 2009-2010. (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Colonial National Historic Park, 2011. (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Colonial National Historic Park: Hogg House, 2011. (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Hampton Roads Bridge Tunnel, undated. (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - I-64 Peninsula Study, 2011. (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Claytor Lake, 2009. (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Route 3 Project in Westmoreland County, 2004. (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - New Route 460, 2007. (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Reedy Creek Mitigation Bank, 2011. (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Dulles Airport, 2005-2012. (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Fort Hunt Park, 2011. (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Maggie Walker Richmond Battlefields, 2004. (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Quantico, 2010. (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Quantico Programmatic Agreement, 2011. (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - York River Shoreline, 2010. (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - United States Coast Guard: Yorktown, 2010-2011. (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Colonial National Historic Park: Dominion Power Underground, 2010. (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - NASA Langley, 2010. (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - George Washington-Jefferson National Forest, undated. (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Occoneechee State Park, 2010. (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Arlington National Cemetery, 2012. (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - I-95 HOT Lanes, 2009. (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - I-64, 2011-2012. (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Lyndham Hill, 2012. (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - Route 3 in Culpeper, 2011. (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Bridge Replacement on Route 6 in Rivanna, 2011. (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Route 460, 2011. (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - South Boston Energy, 2011. (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - Wilton, 2006-2007. (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - Federal Energy Regulatory Commission, 2009-2011. (Box 19, Folder 48)